### **Blake Collins**

(425) 931-8936 23601 56<sup>th</sup> Ave W Unit 2115 Mountlake Terrace, WA 98043 www.github.com/BlakeACollins blakeac369@gmail.com

#### **Professional Summary**

Hello! I discovered a couple years ago that I really enjoy web design and development. I have been working hard to learn as much as I can to make a career change. I am a soon to be graduate of Treehouse's Front-End Web Developer bootcamp. I have a strong interest/ passion for front end development and looking forward to gaining some real-world experience!

## **Education**

Mountlake Terrace High School Mountlake Terrace, WA GPA: 3.4 Graduation Date: 06/2008

#### **Certifications**

Front End Web Developer Techdegree Currently enrolled

Treehouse

Web Design Completed: 03/02/2020

Treehouse

CompTIA ITF+ Obtained: 7/13/2019

Intro to Programming Nanodegree

Udacity Completed: 05/01/2019

Grow with Google Challenge: Android Basics Nanodegree

Udactiy Completed: 04/11/2018

MTA 98-349

Microsoft Windows Operation Fundamentals Completed: 10/14/2017

Java Programming

Edmonds Community College Completed: 09/07/2017

#### **Technical Skills**

Strong: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery

**Knowledgeable**: Vue, JSON, Python

#### **Work History**

Jr. Systems Engineer, March 2020 to Present

Universal Mac - Kirkland, WA

- Provide IT support and management to 50-200 computers.
- Traveling on-site to clients to deploy new technologies.
- Install client software, troubleshoot issues, research, and design new solutions.
- Help automate client system tracking, monitoring, and rollouts.
- Track, resolve, and document trouble tickets.
- On-site and remote ongoing support of existing IT infrastructure.

Quality Control Inspector, 04/08/2019 to 02/20/2020

King Machine – Mukilteo, WA

- Perform in process and final inspection of light assemblies and detail parts per ISO9001 requirements.
- Receiving and inspecting hardware.
- Shipping and part mark inspection.
- Final quality validation prior to inventory.
- Identify, segregate, and maintain records for non-conforming material.
- Preform First Article Inspection (FAI's)
- Familiarity with Geometric Dimensions and Tolerances (GD&T)
- Proficient with Microsoft Office products.

Assembly Technician 2, 12/23/2015 to 04/05/2019

Accra Manufacturing Inc.- Bothell, WA

- Worked directly with QA personnel to identify and correct defects.
- Inspected all work for quality and compliance with design standards.
- Responsible for achieving production requirements.
- Made sure that products were produced on time and are of good quality.
- Fabricated large and small parts per drawing and assembled parts as required.
- Planned, scheduled and delegated daily work.
- Familiarity with computer-based MRP data entry.

- Experience with Business Quality Management System (BQMS) procedures.
- Lean Manufacturing and 6S experience.

Assembly Mechanic, 10/2013 to 12/2015 B/E Aerospace – Marysville, WA

- Experience with pneumatic tools, drills presses, belt sanders, surface grinders, pin drills and polishers, die grinders, and hand deburring tools.
- Responsible for building ottomans, closets, bunks, stowage bins, ceiling panels, vanities, and lavatories.
- Appling decorative laminate.
- Reading blueprints and engineering drawings.
- Complying with FAA building procedures.
- Inspecting hardware, panels, and builds.

*Grocery Team Member*, 09/2011 to 10/2013 Whole Foods Market – Mountlake Terrace, WA

- Used pallet jacks and hand trucks to move merchandise to the sales floor for stocking.
- Purchased new inventory according to expected regular and holiday demand.
- Checked the quality of products and removed defective items.
- Maintained a safe, neat and clean working environment at all times.
- Completed cycle counts and monthly inventory.
- Rotated grocery products ensuring that expired or spoiled items were immediately removed and adhered to the "first in, first out" rule.
- Recommended products to customers to drive sales.

# **Achievements**

Eagle Scout

November 14, 2006

**Blake Collins** 

(425) 931-8936 23601 56<sup>th</sup> Ave W Unit 2115 Mountlake Terrace, WA 98043 www.github.com/BlakeACollins blakeac369@gmail.com